[footsteps]
[deep rumble]
[electricity buzzing]
[man] Listen to me, okay?
You need to hear this.
I love you.
I love you, and you matter.
You are the smartest, funniest,
most creative person I know.
Not to mention gorgeous.
You're a fucking queen,
and you're gonna crush today.
So go get that shit.
[blows kiss]
-[up-beat electronic music]
-[digital beep]
[music switches with video]
[synthwave-pop music]
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Um...
[clears throat]
[girl reading out loud]
[woman] If we do come back
Monday morning,
lock the house before
you go to school,
but we should be back
Sunday night.
[man] Unless we party too hard.
Woo, marriage.
Marie, leave the wine.
It smooths out your driving.
We'll be back Sunday night.
Hey, don't just hold it.
Put it on, try it on, come on.
Let's see how it fits.
This is gonna be amazing.
Marie, look at this.
[Marie] Clay,
could you hurry up?
We're gonna be late
for the rehearsal dinner.
[Clay] Uh-- This is amazing.
I'm just getting a
photograph to
show all our friends, okay?
College man,
start of a new chapter.
There's plenty
of food in the fridge.
Do your homework and no friends.
-Clay.
-Uh-uh, I'm hurrying
as fast as I can, darling.
No, no, no, no, no,
no need to lend a helping hand.
-What?
Hey, kids...
make sure to feed Ruthie,
and walk her twice a day
so she can poop, okay?
Be safe.
And Ruthie...
take care of the kids, okay?
[Marie] No guests.
And don't do anything stupid.
Honor thy mother and father.
Actually,
honor thy father first.
Bye!
[guy and girl] Bye!
[both] Dibs. I said it first.
Fuck you.
-I'm having someone over.
-No, you're not.
-Hey, when I go to college,
you can do whatever
you want for a whole
-year in this house.
-That is not true.
-You know that they never leave
like this.
-Yes, they do.
Yeah, you're about to be at
college where you can do
whatever you want.
-I'm having a friend over.
-You don't have any friends.
You can't have anyone over.
-[guy] Okay.
-[girl] I'm serious.
[guy] Oh, you're serious,
are you?
[girl] Is it your weird
girlfriend?
Yeah, it's my weird,
hot, amazing girlfriend.
[girl] Gross.
Fuck, fine. Just stay in your
room and be quiet.
Don't tell me
what to do, Cassie.
It's unbecoming.
If you don't, I'll tell mom and
dad
-you fucked on the couch.
-Then I'll just show
them where you hide your weed.
Stay in your fucking room, Max.
And you're walking Ruthie.
It's your turn.
-Rock, paper, scissors.
-[Max] No.
-[Cassie] Yes. Yes.
-No.
-You just always get what you
want, don't you?
Yeah, Cassie. I'm stoked.
[Cassie] I need this.
-[sighs]
-[synthwave, pop music]
Max.
-Max.
-[door squeaks and shuts]
[music fades]
[pop-rock music]
Okay.
[nervous chuckle]
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
[Cassie reading out loud]
[message sends]
-[music continues]
-[Cassie squeals excitedly]
[light panting]
Okay. Alright.
[music continues]
[imitating Blake] Wow, Cassie,
this is the perfect temperature.
[continues imitating] I'm sorry
I didn't come over, Cassie.
Really should have been there.
Would've been sick.
[notification beeps]
-[music stops]
-[thud]
[doorbell rings]
Max?
-Max!
-What?
-Is that her?
-[Max] Don't worry about it.
[Cassie] I am fucking
worried about it.
[Max] Well...
...don't.
-[door opens]
-Hey, baby.
[girl] Hey.
-Oh, hi, Ruthie.
-[Cassie] Hey.
-Oh, hey. How are you?
-[Cassie] Hi.
It's so good to see you,
and I love that top.
Unfortunately, we're not allowed
to have people over while our
-parents are in Palm Springs.
-[Max] Okay.
I'm afraid you're gonna
have to go.
That reminds me.
Where's your
imaginary friend?
I'm confused.
She wants to use the house
and doesn't want
us to use the house, but she
doesn't have any friends.
Ah, of course that's not true.
-You're so cute.
-No, that's not true.
Your morally-vacant boyfriend
is lying to you.
He's met my friends.
Who? Emma?
'Cause I haven't seen her
in like a year.
-Where is she?
-She's not coming.
For your information,
my friend is a boy.
[girl] Oh, wait, a boy?
You're having a boy over?
That's right.
Yeah, that's right.
-I am.
-Okay, who? Spill.
Hey, she's lying.
No one's coming.
-Yes, he is.
-[Max] Really?
Yeah, really, you douche.
Roar, okay, feisty.
-I like her.
-Whatever.
When no one
shows up, I'll be right.
Okay.
Well, I'm rooting for you.
You got this.
[footsteps receding]
[sighs]
[slow pop music]
[light chuckle]
-[smooching]
-[chuckle]
You are such a sweetie.
You are such a cutie.
[soft moan]
[imitating] I'm Max,
the tough, hard, manly wrestler.
[light chuckle]
Baby, um, do you think we could
role-play with your leotard?
It is a singlet.
-I told you it is a singlet.
-[girl chucking] Stop-- stop--
Stop it. Stop.
Stop.
[Max] I'm done. I'm done.
You can release me.
Let me go.
I'm not going to tickle you.
-Okay, I'm trusting you. Okay.
-[Max] Yeah, let me go.
Just gonna...
[swooshes]
Okay, now I'm done. I promise.
Okay, can you be serious
for a second, though,
because I have
to tell you something.
[Max] Okay,
I will be very serious.
[hums unseriously]
I'm serious.
[imitating voice] I'm so ready
to be so serious
with you, Harry.
-[girl] Okay.
-That's more Voldemort again.
I was going to tell you,
but you have to guess.
What do you have to tell me?
-W-- well, you have to guess.
-[kissing]
[Max] Okay.
Um, what?
D-- do you not know
what guess means?
Okay, what?
What do you want to tell me?
-Guess! Guess!
-What do you wanna--
Okay, I am guessing.
Okay, let me go.
Jesus, you're strong.
What do you want to tell me?
-What?
-I heard back
from the financial aid office.
In Michigan?
And?
I got it.
They're gonna cover
half my tuition.
That makes me so happy.
Come here.
[girl] Ooh...
[singing]
♪ You're my whiskey, Sarah ♪
-♪ It's easy on the eyes ♪
-[chuckling] Stop!
♪ Have a drink with me ♪
♪ And it's 4 a.m.
And I don't give a damn ♪
-♪ Moonshine down on me ♪
-[chuckling]
♪ Moonshine down on me ♪
Okay, okay, okay, okay,
I get it, I get it.
Oh, you got to tap out.
You can't get out.
No, I can't.
You're trying to escape.
-No, you got to tap out.
-I can't.
Alright, alright, alright.
-You are released.
-[indistinct]
You are released.
And I'm so proud of you.
[electronic pop music]
No, no, no.
No, no--
Maybe. No.
Okay.
[sighs]
[groans]
[digital chime]
[notification beeps]
[light chuckle]
[knocking]
[music fades]
-[knocking]
-I'll get it!
-Hey.
-Hi, Oliver.
I've been trying to ring this
for like 10 minutes.
Oh, you know, [stutters]
we kiss that when we enter.
Uh...
May I... enter?
[chuckles]
[stutters]
-Yeah, pl-- please.
-[Oliver whispering] Okay.
[sniffing]
Whoa, fuck, what i--
what is that?
What's what?
Are you wearing cologne?
Uh, yeah.
Did you put
the entire bottle on?
[chuckles nervously]
No.
Oh, hello, hello.
So, uh, what you wanna do?
Let's go upstairs.
So this is he?
Yep.
Sky, Oliver, Oliver, Sky.
-Hello.
-[Sky] Hey.
Um, you go to [indistinct]
with Cassie?
Uh, I do.
Oh, my gosh, wow.
That's...
...so interesting.
My God, wow. Well, you guys
have a good night, all right?
Um, Sky, I was thinking
and, like, call me crazy, but,
uh, what if all
four of us went in the jacuzzi?
[Sky] Totally.
Oh, my God, yeah.
-[Oliver] That sounds cool.
-[Max] Babe,
[stuttering] babe, no, let's--
let's not do that.
It's gonna be so fun.
Like, we can hang out.
I feel like I haven't
really talked to you.
Say less. I'm so in.
We don't want to, like, intrude
on their night, though,
right? 'Cause they got this
whole thing going.
Max, she's your sister.
I never get
to hang out with her,
and I just want to get
to know her better.
Oh, Sky, me too.
Um, but Oliver doesn't have
a bathing suit.
Uh, I did not bring
a bathing suit. No, I-- I...
You can borrow one
of Max's, right, Max?
No. No, you can't.
Oh, baby, come on.
Yeah, come on.
No, you can--
you can use your boxers.
I'm actually a brief's guy.
Don't be rude to my guest, Max.
Right, Sky?
Ow.
Four fresh beers right here.
You're welcome. Oliver...
-Thank you.
-...for you.
-[chuckling] You're so welcome.
Oh, my God, Sky.
Your tits look so good
in that top.
Girl, thank you so much.
-You are so sweet.
-Yeah, I'm honestly jealous.
-Stop.
Your body is amazing.
You're too sweet.
I think you guys
both look amazing.
[pop music on speakers]
And Max is so handsome.
Uh-- So, how did you two
lovebirds get together?
Yeah, how did
you two get together?
That is a great question.
Max?
[blows raspberry]
Um,
-I can't remember.
-Mm.
Well, I can.
My mind is like...
...one of those metal things
that you step on in the woods.
Uh-- a steel trap?
Yes.
Okay, points for Oliver.
Points.
[chuckle]
[Sky] Well, so, it was actually
English class.
And it was a
school-shooter drill.
Oh, we have those at our school.
Everyone has those, Oliver.
All right, well,
how often are you guys'?
'Cause ours are bi-weekly.
Well, do you mean twice a week
or every other week?
[spits]
It's so crazy
that that word means both.
-Totally.
-What?
Okay, well,
ours are twice a week.
We were once a week,
but we just
-got bumped up to twice a week.
-[Sky] Huh.
Okay, well, so
I'm under the desk, right?
Crouched.
I have my wood-proof folder out.
Oh, I love those.
-[light chuckle]
-And I turn around,
and I catch him staring
at me like a total creep.
Ew!
Creepy!
Was it love
at first creepy stare?
[Sky] Mm...
Yeah, I kind of think it was.
-Yeah. Oh...
-[Max] Yeah, it was.
[Oliver] What better time
to kindle a romance
than when death
is upon us? I--
Seize the day!
Carpe diem, chaliceo!
Well done, Max!
Dude, you are so irritating.
Noted. I'll-- um--
I'll put that
in my feedback log.
So you know Cassie from school?
Uh-- yeah, I actually asked her
to homecoming last year.
-Okay.
-Really?
She never responded.
Oh, must have missed it.
[Max] Wow, that's very cool.
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
Oliver, I actually
recall that my
extremely popular sister here
didn't end up going
to homecoming at all.
Um, well, y-- you know, I--
I'm not sure that that makes me
feel any better, but,
you kn-- we're hanging out now,
and that's all that matters.
That is so sweet.
Max, you should take notes.
Aw, did you hear that?
-Take notes on Oliver.
-Yeah. Take notes on me.
You know what, Oliver,
don't feel bad.
Max didn't even invite me
to his bar mitzvah.
That's because I was 13,
and we didn't even
go to the same school.
Yeah, and I'm still not over it.
Yeah, that's such a shame.
He has the voice of an angel.
You should have heard him--
Max, Max, sing her
-your Haptura portion.
-Fuck off.
Haptura, Haptura, Haptura,
-Haptura, Haptura.
-Oh, okay-- Hey, hey,
hey, let's go upstairs, okay?
Because I have something
I wanna show you.
[Sky] Ooh, okay.
Ooh, is that an innuendo?
-Shut up.
-Hey, be nice.
I have the greatest idea.
[Max] Ooh, what is it?
[slow pop music]
Thank you.
[contained cough]
[light cough]
Okay, fuck.
Cassie, this is really good.
If there's one thing
my sister knows, it's drugs.
Eat me.
I'm lactose intolerant.
Because I'm cheesy?
Is that the joke you're making?
You're difficult to digest, and
I don't have the enzymes for it.
[Sky shushes]
[light chuckle]
[exhales]
Another Friday night.
[sighs]
What?
"Another Friday night?"
I-- Is it not Friday?
I wish there were
more stars in LA.
You know, like, I feel like if
I could see all the stars and...
...constellations,
I would be able to,
like, connect with
my horoscope more deeply.
Oh, are you into astrology?
I mean, I'm not into it.
Like, I wouldn't
say I'm into it.
More... that it discovered me.
-[Cassie] Mm.
-Like-- like, the truth in it.
You know, I found the truth.
Totally.
So it obviously...
really informs
my life in that way.
For sure. I--
I can see that in you.
Wait, really?
That-- That's great.
That-- That means that, um,
the energy that I'm,
like, putting out
here with you guys, but
also just into the universe,
um...
...matches my aura.
-Yes. Your aura.
-Completely. Yeah.
-[coughs]
-You guys are so great.
And can I just say, like,
really cute together?
-Hm...
-Wait, okay, okay. What
are your signs?
Tell me right now.
I was born in January.
-I'm a Libra.
-Okay.
Capricorn. Libra.
Serve, serve.
Capricorn. [stutters]
Earth sign.
So right to business.
Serious.
Kind of practical.
Chop, chop, chop. Um...
Funny.
Oliver's definitely funny.
Libra. Air sign.
So you're charming.
You know, you're-- you're airy.
You're dreamy.
You're easygoing.
-[scoffs and chuckles]
-Um...
[stutters] You can even be
-a little bit naughty.
-[Oliver and Cassie] Ooh.
Yeah, it's clandestine.
It's flirtatious.
Why-- why is it clandestine?
Well, your signs are actually
not traditionally compatible.
-Oh, no.
-[Sky] No, it's okay.
-Are you sure?
-[Sky] Yeah. Yes, girl.
Oh, my God.
Here, move, move.
Yes, it's okay.
Trust me, I really, really know
my shit.
Look, like, opposites attract,
right?
So the differences
in your base natures
are super interesting
to each other,
-right?
-Awesome.
-[Oliver] Really awesome.
-Babe, hey,
let's go upstairs.
Okay, come on.
What if we were having issues?
Like, what would
you recommend then?
Oh... that is a great question.
Okay.
Let the witch... handle it.
So you're both obviously
super ambitious, right?
Like, you care about
school or, like, whatever.
Um, but Capricorn,
not so good about talking about
your emotions, right?
Okay, so communication,
super, super key.
Libra. Social. So you like
to flirt a little bit that can
hurt the Capricorn's feelings.
-[whimpers]
-So keep that in check.
But you guys are, like...
...so good sexually.
-Babe. Nah, come on.
-It's-- it's hot.
It's passionate.
It can be a little bit,
like, obsessive.
-[Cassie] Oh, my God.
I can totally see that
-[Oliver] Totally obsessive.
Um, hey, Sky.
Sky, come here.
-[lighter clicks]
-Yeah?
What?
[scoffs] What the fuck?
[chuckles]
[both girls chuckling]
I love this song.
Should we dance?
I guess.
Yes.
[Sky] Okay.
Alright. Come on.
[Sky chuckling]
Okay...
[yelling and chuckling]
[pop music]
[inaudible]
[music continues on speakers]
-[Sky] Hey.
-Hey.
[kissing]
Okay.
Come here.
Can we go inside?
I have something upstairs
that I wanna show you.
Ooh, a surprise?
-Mm-hmm.
-Hey, Sky.
I have a very
important question to ask you.
How do you feel about Pong?
I'm so good at Pong!
-Fuck you.
Okay, so eye to eye?
Yeah, man. You know any other
way to start this game?
"You know any other way
to start this game?"
[chuckling]
Sorry.
Okay.
-Eye to eye.
-[chuckling]
-Mm.
-Whoa--
-[laughter]
We got
a little bit of competition.
A little bit of that competish.
-Okay.
-Nice.
[chuckling] Yeah, there we go.
[claps]
You got some style, girl.
Please don't
encourage her, babe.
What? You're just in a bad mood
'cause we're losing.
I like you, Sky.
I like you.
All right. Ball's back.
-[light thud]
-[sighs]
-[pop music]
-[light thud]
-Oh, let's go!
-Oh, nice!
-Oh, I needed that.
-[Max] Let's go.
Here we go.
-Let's go! Oh, come on!
-[chuckling]
There it is.
-What?
-Nothing.
[stutters] They just have a nice
celebration after they make it.
Why don't we make this
more interesting?
No.
Yeah. Uh, if we win,
I get to tell an embarrassing
story about my brother.
And if he wins, he can tell an
embarrassing story about me.
-Yes. Yes!
-No.
I want to know more about you
growing up... [stutters] What?
Are you--
-scared that we're gonna lose?
-No, I'm not-- I'm not scared.
My big brother
isn't scared of anything.
-Fuck you.
-And he has
such a way with words.
Okay, you're on. Let's go.
[music continues]
Let's go!
Woo!
[light chuckle]
-Woo!
-[both mumbling]
Fuck.
Hey!
-That counts as one.
-It's alright.
[chuckling] Let's g--
Are you fucking kidding me?
-Nice!
Okay.
[music fades]
[both cheering]
It's okay...
[smooches]
Story time.
Why don't I tell you
about Max's bar mitzvah,
since you weren't there?
-Yes, please.
-Okay, so the ceremony--
the ceremony is great. Voice of
an angel, like I said before.
At the party, this kid Jonah,
who's, like, only there because
our parents are friends,
starts breakdancing,
and all the kids circle around
him, and they're losing
their fucking minds.
-[Oliver] Epic.
-He is a very good dancer.
The rest of the night
is all about Jonah.
He is-- he's the man.
He is a king
amongst Jews and Gentiles alike.
-[Oliver] A god.
-A god!
-A god.
-[chuckling]
Max, obviously pissed,
completely seals Max's thunder,
which Max does not like.
One month later,
Max goes to the state
championship for wrestling.
Don't.
Hey, we made a bet and you lost.
Relax. State championship.
Hey, I'm so serious, Cassie.
Stop.
He's there with our dad.
He makes it to the quarterfinal.
Match is close. Max loses.
To whom, you might ask?
To none other than Jonah.
Oh, plot twist! Consider the
plot twisted! [chuckles]
That is right!
Jonah wrestles too!
Max is obviously pissed
because he thinks he should've
won, and also he has
this bar mitzvah grudge.
Jonah's there
with his whole family.
Ah!
-Jonah's--
-Ah!
-Ah, shut the fuck up!
[overlapping dialogue]
-He has this--
-Ah!
Hey, stop.
You're really pissing me off.
Okay, please, please, please,
please, babe.
Don't listen to this.
Let's just go inside, alright?
Look, now
I really want to hear it.
He has a sister
who's a year older.
Max, out of the tournament,
spends the rest of the day
talking to and flirting
with Jonah's sister,
so while Jonah is competing
in the state final and his
family is watching,
Max sneaks off
with Jonah's sister
and has sex with her
in Jonah's family's hotel room,
and that is how my brother
lost his virginity.
Out of spite.
And the best part is, our dad
was videoing the match
Max lost, and in
the video, you can see when the
referee announces the winner,
Max so angry, glare at Jonah,
and then up at the sister
in the crowd, and then back
at Jonah, and you just know.
And I know where the video is.
When Cassie was 14,
she actually got so depressed
that she started taking oral
narcotics and cutting herself.
-[Sky] Max.
-And this stressed our parents'
already terrible marriage
so much that our
dad moved out
for eight fucking months,
and our mom started
drinking four glasses
of wine, taking tons of pills,
and she got suspicious
that our dad was cheating
on her, so she fucked
an old family friend,
which he still doesn't know
about to this day.
-And when he eventually moved
-[Sky] Hey, stop.
back in, it was terrible,
and it has remained
terrible ever since.
It's kind of a fucking
nightmare, Oliver.
But we don't talk
about it, do we?
Because if we did, it would
make everything worse,
and it would
totally suck. Kinda like
what's happening now, Cassie.
Yeah?
[door shuts]
Jesus, dude.
Who the fuck are you?
[dramatic music]
[muffled scream]
[glass shattering]
[music fades]
Cassie?
[music resumes]
Hey, are you alright?
-Keep them outside.
-What?
Do me a favor.
Can you keep them outside?
-Okay.
-[Cassie] Thanks.
[door shuts]
[items shuffling]
[music continues]
That wasn't okay, Max.
I didn't--
Cassie forced it, okay?
Can we go inside, please?
But the fire's so cozy.
A-- and the stars?
[Max] We're in LA.
There are no stars.
[Sky] There's, um...
Is-- is that-- is that a planet?
I don't know.
Okay, why don't we
let the two of them
be alone, and we can
get some food,
and we can go inside, okay?
Please.
We should make s'mores.
Yeah.
That's a great idea.
[Oliver] Yeah?
-I'll go get the stuff.
-[sighs]
Yeah.
[fire cracking]
[dramatic music]
I don't have anything
against you personally.
W-- well, kind of. But...
...you know you're just here to
piss me off, right?
That's why
my sister invited you.
I sort of figured that out
after a bit, yeah.
That doesn't bother you?
A little.
Not a lot.
What a lot?
Like, enough to get me
to stand up right now and leave?
Yeah.
Are you tryna
get rid of me, Max?
Yeah.
You're a pawn, man.
That doesn't bother you?
I mean, that'd bother me.
Eh, only a pawn
if I'm playing the game.
Well, you're--
you're in the game.
She texted you,
and you showed up.
You're-- you're in it.
[door closes]
[Sky] Golden brown sun?
Okay.
♪ Marshmallow,
banana, chocolate ♪
♪ Marshmallow, banana
Chocolate, Graham Cracker ♪
I'm gonna go check on Cassie.
[clears throat]
[screen buzzing]
[beep]
[soft piano music]
[woman] Check.
[man] Huh, cute.
[woman] Checkmate.
[man] You got some nice moves.
[Sky singing indistinctly]
-[metal clanking]
-[Sky yells]
[woman] Well, a deal's
a deal, Mr. Man.
[Mr. Man] Is that what you're
calling it?
-[Max] Turn it off!
-[woman] And...
-It's not of you!
It's not of you!
-Turn it off! Turn it--
-What is this?
-[Mr. Man] ...an understanding?
-[Sky] Max? Max...
-[woman] I thought you were a
man of your word.
[Mr. Man] And who says I'm not?
-[woman] Don't play coy with me.
-[Oliver] What?
[Mr. Man] I wouldn't dream
of playing coy
-with you.
-[Oliver] What?
[Mr. Man] By the way, where'd
you learn to play?
-Hello?
-[woman] Chess?
-That's their dad.
-[woman] Central Park.
[Mr. Man] You got skill.
Maybe it's just a drama.
He's moonlighting as an actor.
[woman] Hearts aren't what I'm
interested in playing with.
-[Mr. Man groans]
-[everyone yells]
-[beep]
-[movie stops]
There are like 15 of these!
So I'm guessing
that wasn't your mom?
-I swear to God--
-Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, I hate to say this.
Like, I really, really, really
hate to say this, but...
...I kind of feel like we have
to watch a couple more.
Like, what if that wasn't
the only other woman?
What if there's, like, more?
[stutters] Look.
This is from last month.
[shower turning on]
[water running]
-Wow.
-[Clay] Mind if I join you?
-That's somebody else.
-[woman 2] What?
She m-- must have
back problems, right? I--
[woman 2] I'm sorry.
I can't hear you over
the sound of the shower.
You'll have to join me.
[shower curtains slide]
-[woman moans]
-[Sky] Oh, turn it off.
[moaning]
[up-beat tempo music]
[beep]
[woman 3] Is this seat taken?
[Clay] On my fucking face.
[woman 3] Oh, wow.
[beep]
[Clay] The honorable
Judge Evans presiding.
[woman 4] Bailiff, I seem to
have forgotten my robe.
[moaning]
[beep]
[woman 5] I'll huff
and I'll puff
and I'll blow this house down.
[Clay squealing] No!
-No! Not my ho--
- [movie stops]
So...
are you gonna, like...
...tell your mom?
Get him out of here!
Why the fuck is he still here?
Don't tell me what to do, Max!
Don't ever tell me what to do!
Don't ever tell me
what to fucking do!
You...
...should go.
Um, this is...
...a family issue.
Yeah, yeah, I--
I'll get out of your hair.
Um, this goes without
saying, but,
as a favor to me, please
don't tell anybody about this.
Yeah, of course.
-Bye.
Whoa.
Oh, fuck. Shit, sorry.
Was that a mistake?
That was a mistake.
Sorry.
Put this back
wherever you found it,
and never,
ever mention it again.
Okay?
[Sky] At least you guys
found it instead of your mom.
[footsteps receding]
[thud]
[line ringing]
-[Marie] Hello?
-Mom?
-[Marie] Who is this?
-Mom, it's me.
Oh, Cassandra. Are you calling
me from the home phone?
Yes.
You need to come home.
It's an emergency.
[Sky] Okay, hey, hey,
hello, hello.
Max, hey, hey, hey. No!
There's nothing
to talk about, Sky.
I don't want to talk about it.
[sighs]
Just give me
one second, alright?
Fuck!
Max?
Max, hey.
Is that champagne?
-It was.
-Hey, Max, stop.
-Max, stop. Hey, hey.
-Cassie came in here.
-I had a whole--
-Leave Cassie alone.
-What is going on with you?
-[indistinct]
You just saw your dad...
Why was there
champagne in the bathroom?
[beep]
[fire sizzling]
[plastic rustling]
[Blake] Yo.
[pop music]
[music stops]
Hey.
Nice place.
Thanks.
[chuckles nervously]
What--
What are you doing--
Oh, you seem confused.
Um, did you not get my text?
I said I'd deliver.
No, I-- I don't have my phone.
Um, I left it charging.
It-- it died.
[Blake chuckles] All good.
All good.
Do you have a dog?
Yeah.
-Cool.
-Hey, Blake,
my parents--
Blake.
-[Blake] You alright?
-Yeah, yeah. Um--
It-- It's actually just, um...
I'm so, so sorry.
It's just a really bad time.
There's been, like,
a family emergency,
and my parents
-are on their way home, so...
-[Blake] Oh, shit...
Uh, is--
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Um, yeah. [stutters]
It's just that I'm not going to
be able to hang out or do the
chemistry lab, I mean...
So...
Do you know
when they're going to be back?
Yeah, uh, yes.
In a few hours.
They're coming back,
then-- so, they'll be back.
[Blake] So...
...we could work for a few hours
and then I'll leave before
they're supposed to get here.
-[nervous chuckle]
-[chuckle] Sorry, I--
I don't mean to be pushy.
It's just...
This is literally the only time
I can do it this weekend.
And when I saw your text,
I was like,
"Oh, she is so right.
We've got to work
on this chemistry."
[light chuckle]
Do you have your stuff?
[Blake groans] God. N--
No.
I forgot it at home.
But hey, I should be fine.
'Cause we could just
do it all on your laptop.
[pop music]
[music stops]
Here you go.
Okay...
I got into Michigan.
-What?
-I got in.
You-- you applied?
Yeah.
And you didn't tell me?
I wanted to surprise you.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I mean, I was gonna
do it earlier tonight,
before my family fucked
everything up,
but...
So, you know.
Surprise, Sky.
[chuckles]
Max, I mean,
you got into
Stanford and Dartmouth.
-Yeah.
-I'm not exactly surprised
that the Michigan State
University accepted you.
Well, sure.
But I mean, you are surprised,
I'm sure,
that I'm going with you.
-What?
-I'm going with you.
No. No, you're not.
We're going
to Michigan together.
No, we're not.
-We are. That's th--
-No.
You got into Dartmouth.
You're going to Dartmouth.
You're wrestling for Dartmouth.
Okay?
-I-- I can wrestle at Michigan.
-No.
-You love Dartmouth.
-I love Michigan.
Why are you lying
to me right now?
Why do you think
I'm lying to you?
And also, shouldn't you be
excited about this?
Yeah, obviously I'd be excited
if it were true.
But I know you'd only consider
Michigan because of me.
It's a nice bonus.
[sighs]
[stuttering] So...
Um, yeah, these are
just my notes on how he said to
do the electrophoresis data.
You have really pretty
handwriting.
Thanks. [light chuckle]
Um,
yeah, if you wanted to do the--
the abstract,
then I could do the method, or
um, maybe you--
I could do the method
and you could do the abstract.
I have these-- these
notebooks,
so you could handwrite
or, um, I could
handwrite and you
cou-- uh, you could type
whatever you want to do.
Yeah, um, let me write.
I'll, uh-- [clicks tongue]
I'll take the pink notebook.
[chuckles] Okay.
[light chuckle]
The discussion
questions look hard.
You know, I'm really glad that
you're my chemistry partner,
[chuckling] because
I don't get any of this.
-Hey, are you excited for prom?
-[chokes]
[coughs]
-[coughing]
-Are-- are you okay?
Totally.
-Just-- [coughs] Wrong pipe.
-Hmm.
-Uh, can I get you anything?
-[coughing]
Water?
[chuckles] That's funny.
Pretty funny.
-I'm a funny guy.
-Oh, really?
In class?
Come on.
Yeah, yeah,
you're pretty funny in class.
Thank you.
How's that method coming?
Oh, uh, [scoffs] this method?
-Oh, it's great.
-I love methods.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
I never knew you were so
enthusiastic about school.
[scoffs] I love it.
Um...
Well, history.
English.
Electrons.
[chuckles] What about
the electrons?
Well, they're--
they're really small.
Like, s-- super tiny.
[stutters] So small.
Yeah, like teeny
tiny little electrons.
Wow, you're weird.
No, I would never--
I'm not.
-What?
-Hm?
Your TikToks are so good.
Um, I'm sure that you get
that all the time, though.
Uh... Yeah, yeah.
[chuckles]
Yeah, yeah.
What's like--
what is your method
for making those?
The-- the TikToks?
Uh, I mostly just do the trends.
That must be so interesting.
Yeah, um, I-- Sometimes I just
sit and talk to the camera.
-Yeah, I've seen those.
-Yeah, they're--
they're great for exposure.
But what about you?
I mean, I've seen you around,
but we don't really talk much.
What you-- What are you into?
[stuttering] Yeah, no, totally.
I agree, um--
I feel like I see you around
school and online and stuff,
and I just-- I think that we'll
vibe really well.
Um, like in chemistry class,
you're always like-- [stutters]
Wow.
Yeah.
Weed.
[smacks lips]
And beer.
Oh, my God.
-My breath?
-[Blake] No, no, no.
You're good.
It's cool.
It's cool. [chuckles]
[stutters]
G-- give me one second.
[under her breath]
Yes, yes!
[breathing rapidly]
Yes!
Max, you can't make
your college decision for me.
[scoffs]
Why not? I-- I love you.
Baby, I love you, but we're
just gonna have to be
in different places
for a couple years.
No, it's not-- it's not a chance
that I'm willing to take.
Hell, it's not only your choice.
Well, I can't do long distance.
-Why not?
-I can't do it.
Can't or won't?
Okay, what if it doesn't work?
Baby, of course it's gonna work.
And what-- what if it doesn't?
[Sky] Okay,
then at least we tried.
It will work for as long
as we want it to.
And what if you
stop wanting it to?
[Sky] What if you stop wanting
it to?
-I won't. I'm not gonna.
-Wait, if you
say yes to Michigan,
you'll be forcing me to break up
with you.
Wh-- Why would you even say
something like that?
Look, you can't make
this decision for me.
And what if it's
the right decision?
Well, it's not, okay?
And then you'll have made
the wrong decision for me.
Why are you so worried?
Because I wanna be with you.
Yeah-- Well, Max...
...I will not let you use me.
Alright? You are trying
to use me...
...as this kinda escape route
to get away
-from your family.
-I am getting
out of here either way.
Michigan or Dartmouth, it
doesn't make a difference.
I'm going to be nowhere
near my family.
Do you wanna meet someone else?
Is that it?
No, Max, that's not it.
Hey, hey.
[soft pop music]
[turning water faucet on]
[swishing]
-[dog sniffing]
-Ruthie, not now.
-Ruthie, stop.
-[dog whines]
[music turns interesting]
[sighs]
[music fades]
-[beep]
-[exciting music]
[woman] Are you ready for your
prostate exam, Mr. Johnson?
[Clay] As ready
as I'll ever be, Doc.
[woman] If you're uncomfortable,
you could do me first.
[woman moaning]
-[soft pounding]
-[moaning]
Hey!
[woman] Wow, mister...
What the fuck?
-[woman] Wow, mister...
-Give me that, hey--
Stop.
-[moaning on film continues]
-[both grunting]
[Clay] Yes! Yes!
-[Clay] Yes!
- [woman moaning]
[woman moaning]
[existing music in background]
-[woman] You're so generous.
-[both grunting]
[screams]
What the fuck is happening?
-What the fuck?
-[coughing]
-Blake...
-[moaning continues]
Blake, look at me. Are you okay?
-[Blake] What--
-[Cassie] Are you okay?
Stand up.
[grunting]
Max, what is going on?
What the fuck, man?
Cassie, who the fuck is this,
you fucking idiot?
He was filming it.
-What?
-[Max] He was filming it.
So you attacked him?
He was taking it,
probably to post it
online or some shit.
Our dad, Cassie.
Our fucking dad.
Porn of our dad on that phone.
[moaning continues]
Do you understand how serious
that is?
Max, get off of him.
-Stop.
-[Blake] Stop.
-I said stop.
-What the fuck is going on?
[Blake grunting] Help.
-Who is that guy?
-Help me.
-[Max] Hey, face ID.
Help, please.
-What?
-[Max] Face ID!
[grunting]
Go.
[moaning on film continues]
What are you doing?
I'm fucking deleting the video
of our dad's dick.
[door squeaks]
Hello?
[exciting music from far away]
[muffled moaning]
This fucking douche
definitely has some
incriminating shit on here.
Deleted tweets,
dick pics, nudes.
-So?
-[Max] So,
I'm going to send myself
some blackmail.
So he doesn't tell everyone we
know about our dad's porn...
...that you just showed him
because you are a sad,
pathetic person.
I didn't show him,
you piece of shit.
And then you let him go.
[loud moaning]
[soft pounding]
-[beep]
-[moaning stops]
[screen buzzing]
Hey.
Hey, Oliver.
I forgot my backpack.
Dude, what is
with this fucking kid?
Hey, get the fuck
out of here, man.
-Leave our house. Stop.
-[Blake] Help.
Is that Blake Sheviot?
Cassie, get him the fuck out of
here while I
clean up your fucking mess.
Yeah, normally I'm--
I'm pretty chill.
Like, I think I'm generally
a pretty chill guy.
But I do feel like I need to
know what's going on here.
-[Blake struggling]
-Um...
...he and my brother
have had beef for years.
And he showed up
and they fought and Max won.
[Max] That is not what happened.
She invited him over to hook up.
[dramatic music]
Is that true?
N-- no, of course not.
You know Max,
you spent all day with him.
What is your impression
of my brother?
He's an asshole.
Exactly.
But he doesn't strike me
as a liar.
[Blake struggling]
-[mumbling]
-[grunting]
-[thud]
-Oh!
[music continues]
You have this, babe.
Woop!
[trash bin rustling]
[music continues]
If me having this doesn't keep
his mouth shut,
we are so beyond fucked.
You're so beyond fucked.
[Cassie] Why would you
attack him?
How could you possibly think
that that was a good solution?
A good solution?
[chuckles]
Let me get this
straight, Cassie.
After we discover
that our dad has been
making porn,
you invite a guy
over so that you can bone him.
And then you show him the porn.
I didn't show him.
He found it while
I was in the bathroom.
Okay, so you're fucking stupid
enough to let him find it.
And I didn't invite him over
after we f-- found the DVDs. I--
I invited him over
hours ago, and then
he just--
he showed up unexpectedly.
[Max] Great. Amazing!
It makes a huge difference
how he got here.
Oh, great.
I'm sensing some sarcasm here.
I'm going to kill you.
Be my guest! Do it!
-Do it!
-That's right. Back to slitting
your wrists,
I'd be doing you a favor.
[smack]
[dramatic music]
[items squeak]
[cutlery clanking]
[cutlery clanking loudly]
He's back.
[music continues]
[door squeaks]
I'm gonna head out.
Come on.
Look, I get it.
You wanted Blake,
and you got me.
Now, I'd like to excuse myself.
Nope, no, no.
You are not leaving
with this impression of me.
[Oliver] Oh, no, no.
This is an impression of you.
[mimicking voice]
"Hi, I'm Cassie.
I'm going to use poor oblivious
Oliver to get
back at my brother who I have an
unhealthy relationship with,
but let's not
impact that right now."
Finished?
For now.
-[music continues]
-Hey, Max, stop.
-What? What?
-[Sky] Stop.
-You're being...
-[Max] Let's just--
Please, can we just do
this later? There's a fucking
stranger in my house. What?
I'm sorry for slapping you.
No, you're not.
No, I'm not.
I'm a sweetheart.
I am.
But you're pushing it.
You're being
terrible to Cassie, and...
...you're now taking it out
on this guy?
Like, what are you going to do
when you find him, Max?
Kill him?
-[music continues]
-[wood squeaking]
[Max] I love you.
Sorry.
Hey, let's look calmly,
but carefully together.
I'm really sorry.
[stutters]
That was so fucked up, and I--
I shouldn't have...
Done it? Yeah, I know.
Can I go now?
-No.
-No?
No, I-- I-- I'm telling you,
I'm nothing--
Do you think I'm stupid?
I-- I knew after 15 minutes
you were just tryna
piss your brother off.
And yeah, [stutters]
it bothered me
a little, but...
not more than I wanted
to get to know you.
Or for you to get to know me.
Like, actually take a second
to get to know me.
I do, I do know you now.
But you hooked up
with Blake after I left.
[chuckles]
I mean, what the fuck?
[Cassie]
Okay, yes, that's all true.
-Awesome. Oh,
-But I'm...
-really awesome.
-I'm sorry.
[Oliver] Really, really awesome.
Would you just shut up for a
second?
[Oliver] Oh, this is shitty.
This is a really shitty thing
you did-- or are doing.
[Cassie] Yes, okay, yes, yes.
Yeah, it is really shitty,
and I'm sorry, but just like,
don't overreact.
Overreact? [chuckles]
Overreact?
Yes.
Are you serious right now? I--
Do you have any idea how this
makes me feel? [stutters]
I'm not only second place
to fucking Blake Sheviot,
[stutters]
I'm a pawn.
I'm literally a pawn,
like your brother said.
Oh, come on, Oliver.
I thought...
I thought you were
the guy who was like
so sure of himself and who
he is, and his, like...
...philosophies on the world
and high school, and he doesn't
give a shit about
what other people
think about him or do.
What?
[stutters]
Of course-- of course I fucking
care what other people
think about me. Wh--
What kind of person
have you ever met
in your life that
doesn't care what
other people think?
Are you insane?
I'm 17!
I care what people think!
[footsteps]
[wood squeaking]
[Oliver in background] We're all
just faking whatever...
[Olive continues indistinctly]
[Cassie] I know that! That's
why... like, nobody knows--
[music continues]
[kibbles rustle]
[dog panting]
[ominous music]
[dog huffs]
Okay.
-[breathing heavily]
-[pop]
-[inhaler sprays]
-[deep breath]
[gasping]
[music fades]
[door slams]
Why did you kiss me?
-Look, can we not? I'll just go.
-[Cassie] Why did you kiss me?
I like you.
And I thought we were having
a fun night together.
Until the--
until the porn stuff.
But until then,
I thought we were having a
fun night together and we were
really starting to get along.
Despite your original reasons
for having me over.
I-- I thought you were having
a good time, too.
I was.
So...
But, uh--
What do you think this is?
Are you--
are you trying to fuck me?
What? No! No, I-- I mean,
not that I would be
opposed, you kn-- because,
you know, I think you're
gorgeous and everything,
but-- but--
[stuttering] No, no, no, I mean,
um, date you, or--
Date me?
Yes.
I meant the possibility of in
the future, you know,
not just after, like, one
night of us hanging out again
'cause, you know, I'm not-- not
not like crazy or anything,
but-- but, yeah,
because I like you
and I thought
you liked me, too?
[intense music]
[dog huffs]
[dog whines]
[barking]
[sobs]
[scratching]
[dog growling]
-[inhaler sprays]
-[scratching]
Alright, you fucking bitch.
[deep thud]
Wow.
[chuckling]
Good dog. Good dog.
Hey, guys.
What's her name?
-[pop-rock music]
-Woo! There you go.
Alright, Ruthie, who's a good
dog. Who's a good dog, huh?
[Max] I, uh, texted myself
plenty of stuff in here,
so, you know, don't tell anyone.
Yeah.
Don't tell anyone.
So you can fight, huh?
[chuckles]
Uh, yeah, I can wrestle.
I-- I guess.
I want a rematch.
No.
You know, I, uh...
...I really do like you, Cassie.
I like you too, Blake.
No, I mean, I like-like you.
Uh, maybe we could do something.
We could do the lab on Sunday.
You know, I--
Woop!
I don't think
that that's a great idea.
Yeah.
Um...
W-- Bye, then.
Bye, everybody.
[Max] Don't come back.
Come on, this good girl needs
some water-- some water...
[door closes]
[digital chime]
[music fades]
Mom and Dad
are five minutes away.
You're not that low.
No, Cassie.
[inhales deeply]
[whispers] Oh, my God.
-[Sky] What?
-She-- she told
our parents about the sex tapes.
She wants-- she wants to--
she wants to tell Mom.
You are so fucked up.
-Oh, my God.
-[Cassie] Fuck you, Max.
She has a right to know.
She has a right to know?
That's not why you called them
back here tonight.
In the middle of their trip, you
want a big, dramatic reveal.
You want to burn
this family to the ground.
If I had a daughter and she knew
something about my husband,
I would want her to tell me.
Don't pretend that this is some
mother-daughter bond shit.
Alright?
You can't lie to me, Cassie.
You-- you just wanna destroy us.
Why shouldn't I?
Seriously, do you think they
have a good marriage?
They are a fucking black hole
and you're tryna push me in
and I won't fucking go.
-What?
-[Max] Don't you think we're all
miserable enough without your
insane, theatrical,
pity-party drama?
You make things worse.
You make it harder.
And what do you do, Max?
You separate yourself?
You disappear?
Run away like a fucking coward?
How full of hate must you be
to do something like this?
I'm full of hate?
You're the angriest person
I've ever met.
You're so angry,
it's exhausting.
That and how mean you are.
You're defining characteristic.
Don't fucking talk to me.
I didn't seek you out to have
conversations, okay?
Just leave me alone.
Fine, I'll leave you
alone forever!
[Max] You're fucking psychotic.
I said something about you
cutting yourself
and you call our parents to show
them dad cheating on mom
to get back at me?
Oh, you think
that these are funny?
What? No.
Do you think
that these are funny?
-You know I don't.
-[Cassie] Are you sure?
Are you sure that you don't want
to tell a fun story about them?
I don't-- Cassie,
I don't think they're funny.
You're so-- you don't know.
You-- you have no fucking clue.
[sniffles]
You got yourself to feel
something else
and yet cutting is the
alternative and cutting is...
...just a--
[dramatic music]
[crying]
[sobbing]
Cassie...
...I'm sorry.
Alright? I'm sorry.
I was sorry then, too.
And I'm sorry...
that I didn't...
I didn't--
I wasn't a lot of help.
I know that.
But please don't do this.
[sniffles]
You-- you know when things
were really bad and--
[sniffles] and-- and they were
just screaming at each other
all the time and--
[sniffles] and-- and, it was
because of them but it was also
because of me.
I just-- I felt like I was being
eaten from the inside.
And I looked to you...
...my brother...
...for something, anything.
Hoping to see that there
was someone in there
who could see what I could.
Who was experiencing
something, too.
That I wasn't completely
fucking alone.
[Max] Of course, I--
How could I not?
I'm just as much a part
of this family as you are.
But I never saw that.
We all do
what we have to, Cassie.
Yeah, we do.
[car door shuts]
[Max] Sky, hide upstairs.
What is it now? What is it?
What's the emergency?
[breathing shakily]
Guys?
[music continues]
[Marie] Hello?
We figured it out. Sorry.
[Clay] What?
You figured what out?
[Marie] Yeah, you tell me
exactly why you called,
what the problem was,
why you wouldn't tell
me over the phone,
why you thought
it was an emergency,
how you solved it.
I mean, this--
this is unbelievable.
This is unbelievable.
You can't scare us like this!
You can't scare us like this.
[breathing shakily]
[Clay] Answer your mother.
You almost gave her
a heart attack.
We were worried sick.
This is no good, guys.
No good at all.
This is no good?
Are you serious?
-What? What did I do?
-You can't bring your foot down
a little bit more?
Aren't you gonna do anything?
You have to be
everybody's best friend.
[Clay] You're turning this
on me now?
[Marie] Well,
I'd like a little help
with the parenting.
Would you like
a little drink, Marie?
Can I make you a little drink?
Don't you walk away from me!
I have been traveling
in the car for eight hours.
-We've missed the wedding.
-I have-- First of all,
you didn't want to
go to the fucking wedding.
I have been driving
for eight hours.
You have been sitting
and sleeping.
And all you can say is,
"This is no good"?
-This is no good? God...
-[Clay] Yeah, "It's no good.
"That's what I said.
[Marie] The best you
could come up with.
[Clay] Don't take that
out on me.
[Marie] All you can say is...
[dramatic music]
[sniffles]
You're crying.
-[Blake sobs]
-[music continues]
I've never seen you cry before.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
Me too.
For when you were...
[crying]
I know.
Okay, get off me.
[music continues]
[inaudible]
[door opens]
[sobbing]
[Sky] Hey...
[whispering] Hey, it's okay.
[music continues]
You are nothing like them, Max.
People make long distance sound
harder than it is.
-Yeah?
-[light chuckle]
[music continues]
I have to ask you a question.
I put too much
cologne on, didn't I?
[chuckles]
[up-beat music]
[chuckling]
[music continues]
[music fades]